export const chapter = "Chapter - 14: Simple Past Tense";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What does Simple Past Tense describe?",
          optionA: "Future actions",
          optionB: "Present actions",
          optionC: "Actions that took place in the past",
          correctAnswer: "Actions that took place in the past",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which word order is used for affirmative sentences in Simple Past Tense?",
          optionA: "Subject + Verb in I Form + Object",
          optionB: "Subject + Verb in II Form + Object",
          optionC: "Subject + will + Verb + Object",
          correctAnswer: "Subject + Verb in II Form + Object",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the word order for negative sentences in Simple Past Tense?",
          optionA: "Subject + will + Verb + Object",
          optionB: "Subject + did not + Verb in I Form + Object",
          optionC: "Subject + Verb in II Form + Object",
          correctAnswer: "Subject + did not + Verb in I Form + Object",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In negative sentences, what form of the verb is used with 'did not'?",
          optionA: "Present form (I form)",
          optionB: "Future form (III form)",
          optionC: "Past form (II form)",
          correctAnswer: "Present form (I form)",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the word order for interrogative sentences in Simple Past Tense?",
          optionA: "Interrogative Word + Subject + Verb in I Form + Object?",
          optionB: "Subject + did not + Verb in I Form + Object?",
          optionC: "Subject + Verb in II Form + Object?",
          correctAnswer:
            "Interrogative Word + did + Subject + Verb in I Form + Object?",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When is 'did' used in an interrogative sentence in Simple Past Tense?",
          optionA: "At the end of the sentence",
          optionB: "In the middle of the sentence",
          optionC: "At the beginning of the sentence",
          correctAnswer: "At the beginning of the sentence",
        },
        {
          question: "Which tense is also known as Past Indefinite Tense?",
          optionA: "Present Continuous Tense",
          optionB: "Simple Past Tense",
          optionC: "Future Perfect Tense",
          correctAnswer: "Simple Past Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which form of the verb is used with all subjects in Simple Past Tense?",
          optionA: "Present form (I form)",
          optionB: "Future form (III form)",
          optionC: "Past form (II form)",
          correctAnswer: "Past form (II form)",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In an affirmative sentence, what is the word order for Simple Past Tense?",
          optionA: "Subject + did not + Verb in I Form + Object",
          optionB: "Subject + Verb in II Form + Object",
          optionC:
            "Interrogative Word + did + Subject + Verb in I Form + Object?",
          correctAnswer: "Subject + Verb in II Form + Object",
        },
        {
          question: "Which sentence is in Simple Past Tense?",
          optionA: "I am eating dinner.",
          optionB: "We will go to the beach tomorrow.",
          optionC: "He saw a movie yesterday.",
          correctAnswer: "He saw a movie yesterday.",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Affirmative sentences in Simple Past Tense have the word order: Subject + Verb in ____________ + Object.",
          options: ["II Form", "I Form (s/es)", "III Form"],
          correctAnswer: "I Form (s/es)",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Simple Past Tense, the Past form (II form) of the verb is used with ___________ subjects.",
          options: ["Singular", "Plural", "All"],
          correctAnswer: "All",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Negative sentences in Simple Past Tense have the word order: Subject + did not + ___________ + Object.",
          options: ["Verb in I Form", "Verb in II Form", "Verb in III Form"],
          correctAnswer: "Verb in I Form",
        },
        {
          question:
            'The Present form of the verb (I form) is used with "did not" in all ___________ sentences.',
          options: ["Interrogative", "Affirmative", "Negative"],
          correctAnswer: "Negative",
        },
        {
          question:
            '"I did not go to the picnic" is an example of a ___________ sentence.',
          options: ["Negative", "Affirmative", "Interrogative"],
          correctAnswer: "Negative",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In interrogative sentences, the word order is: Interrogative Word + did + Subject + ___________ + Object?",
          options: ["Verb in I Form", "Verb in II Form", "Verb in III Form"],
          correctAnswer: "Verb in I Form",
        },
        {
          question:
            '"Did she read my letter yesterday?" is an example of a ___________ sentence.',
          options: ["Affirmative", "Negative", "Interrogative"],
          correctAnswer: "Interrogative",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The word order for interrogative sentences in Simple Past Tense starts with the use of ___________.",
          options: ["Interrogative Word", "Subject", "Verb in II Form"],
          correctAnswer: "Interrogative Word",
        },
        {
          question:
            '"When did you go home?" is an example of an interrogative sentence with the interrogative word ___________.',
          options: ["Why", "Did", "When"],
          correctAnswer: "When",
        },
        {
          question: "The Past Indefinite Tense is also known as ___________.",
          options: [
            "Present Continuous Tense",
            "Future Perfect Tense",
            "Simple Past Tense",
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Simple Past Tense",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "The Past Indefinite Tense is also referred to as Simple Past Tense.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Affirmative sentences in Simple Past Tense follow the word order: Subject + Verb in II Form + Object.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Negative sentences in Simple Past Tense use the Past form (II form) of the verb with all subjects.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            'In negative sentences, the Present form of the verb (I form) is used with "did not" in Simple Past Tense.',
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            'Interrogative sentences in Simple Past Tense start with an interrogative word, followed by "did" at the beginning of the sentence.',
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            'The interrogative word "When" is used in sentences like "Did it rain last night?" in Simple Past Tense.',
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "All subjects, whether singular or plural, use the Past form (II form) of the verb in Simple Past Tense.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The word order for negative sentences in Simple Past Tense is: Subject + did not + Verb in I Form + Object.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            'In interrogative sentences, "did" is used in the middle of the sentence in Simple Past Tense.',
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Simple Past Tense describes actions that will take place in the future.",
          optionA: "True",
        optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
